(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) William's parents have been divorced for five years.
Most kids are sad when this happens.
William was happy.
He hated it when his parents were together.
They always fought.
It was annoying to hear them arguing.
He also loves having two homes.
His mom lives in England.
His dad lives in Canada.
William currently lives in Canada.
He goes to England whenever he has a
long holiday.
His mom and dad are all remarried now.
William loves his step-parents.
He also loves his half-siblings.
William loves having two families.
He was never happy when his parents were
together.
They made him choose sides all the time.
Now, he has the best of both worlds.